let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Where is Moai located?",
  answer: "Easter Island",
  options: [
    "New Zealand",
    "Easter Island",
    "Hawaii",
    "America"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "What was the name of the tool used to carve Moai?",
  answer: "Toki",
  options: [
    "Toki",
    "Hammer",
    "Chisel",
    "Metal"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "What is the world’s most visited museum?",
  answer: "Vatican Museums",
  options: [
    "Natural History Museum",
    "British Museum",
    "Tate Modern",
    "Vatican Museums"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "What do moai statues represent?",
  answer: "Ancestral chiefs",
  options: [
    "Ancestral chiefs",
    "Soldier",
    "Commander",
    "God"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "What does 'moai' represent",
  answer: "Nike",
  options: [
    "Venus de Milo",
    "Mona Lisa",
    "Nike",
    "The Thinker"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Who painted ‘The Starry Night’?",
  answer: "Vincent van Gogh",
  options: [
    "Claude Monet",
    "Pablo Picasso",
    "Vincent van Gogh",
    "Salvador Dalí"
    ]
  },
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Where is the real Mona Lisa kept?",
  answer: "Paris",
  options: [
    "London",
    "Paris",
    "New York",
    "India"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the world’s most visited museum?",
    answer: "Vatican Museums",
    options: [
      "Natural History Museum",
      "British Museum",
      "Tate Modern",
      "Vatican Museums"
    ]
},
];



// let questions = [
//     {
//     numb: 1,
//     question: "Where is the real Mona Lisa kept?",
//     answer: "Paris",
//     options: [
//       "London",
//       "Paris",
//       "New York",
//       "India"
//     ]
//   },
//     {
//     numb: 2,
//     question: "Who painted ‘The Starry Night’?",
//     answer: "Vincent van Gogh",
//     options: [
//       "Claude Monet",
//       "Pablo Picasso",
//       "Vincent van Gogh",
//       "Salvador Dalí"
//     ]
//   },

//     {
//     numb: 4,
//     question: "What was the Terracotta Army a part of?",
//     answer: "A tomb",
//     options: [
//       "A tomb",
//       "An art exhibit",
//       "A sculpture contest",
//       "A palace"
//     ]
//   },
//     {
//     numb: 5,
//     question: "What is another name for the Winged Victory?",
//     answer: "Nike",
//     options: [
//       "Venus de Milo",
//       "Mona Lisa",
//       "Nike",
//       "The Thinker"
//     ]
//   },
// ];